Guide to the Richard White papers SC1323
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Books
  - Railroaded: The Transcontinentals and the Making of Modern America
    - S.P. profits, 1872-1874 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Profits - CP + subsidiary, 1872-1873 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Cal Pac, 1875-1877 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Cal or., 1875 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - CP - SP Indians, 1874-1877 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Ft. Yuma, 1877 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Yama, 1877-1878 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Nevada, 1871-1878 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - D.M. Huntington Journal Utah, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - C.P. Nevada politics, 1877 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Oregon, 1873 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - CP. Expenditures by Assoc. + Politic, 1875 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - CA elections - newspaper, 1870-1875 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - San Diego, 1879 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Clippings C.P. + Wilson, 1872 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Wilson Committee, 1872 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Legislation affecting RR, 1870s (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Hyde doituaries, 1882 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Hyde Coll. MS 267 Stanford - Goat Island, lobbying, 1867 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Arde in LA etc, 1871-1872 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Hyde to wife + other personal letters, 1867-1879 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - SF. Alta - Colton trial, 1883-1884 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Colton case, 1889 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - SF call - colton trial, 1884 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - SF chronicle - Colton trial, 1884 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Heidi's summaries, 1882 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Newspapers: panic of 1873 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Misc. newspaper clippings (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Simontan A.P., 1878-1879 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Harpen, 1873 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Newspaper, 1873-1878 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Credit, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Report of Chief Engineer Tod (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Henry Dodge - Engineering Union Pacific, 1909 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Farnham - Dodge, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Wim. J. Pinterton - his personal/ B Rec. (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Court cases - CP/SP (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Legislation, 1868 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Legislation, 1870 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Bond - interest RD (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Legislation, 1870 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Sen. Er completion, 1869 Dec (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - H. Exec., 1870 Dec (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Legislation, 1872 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Legislation, 1873 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Credit Mobiler - Comm (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Legislation, 1874 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Legislation affecting RR, 1875 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Legislation, 1876 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Legislation, 1877 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Legislation, 1878 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Southern Pacific 45th Congress, Ft. Yumen, 1878 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Texas and Pacific 45th Congress, 1878 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Legislation, 1879 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Legislation, 1880 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - C.P. + Texas Pacific, 1872-1879 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Cons. Globe 45th congress, 1878 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Cong. Globe - 41st Cong., 1871-1890 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Cong. Globe - 43rd Cong., 1875 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Cong. Globe - 44th Cong., 1876 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Congressional G., 1871 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Cong. Globe - 42nd Cong., 1872 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Cong. Globe 46th Cong., 1880 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Lewright - "Few Facts" - 1895 Consolidation S.A. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Baldwin Locomotive Work, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Baldwin Locomotives Atchison, Topeler, Santa FP, 1906 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Baldwin Locomotives: Pacific Type Locomotive etc., 1891 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Joel Tarr R.R. Materials, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Locomotive Fireman + Environmental Activists, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - R.R. + Nature, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Harley Amer. RR C. (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Coatsworth - Growth Agent Development, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Peter Tufano - Business Failure, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Tufano, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Mercer: Rates of Return, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Railways: Uneven G. Development (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Stephen Tehudi: Western Tech. Landscapes, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Agrarian Conflicts - Mexico (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Senate Coatswell, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Magliari - P - M. W., 1989 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Texas Politics - See also C.P. T.P. / Seat (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - K. Sources. Mode Rn, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Falls of Saint Anthony (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Steam - Landscape (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - R.R.s: Misc. (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - To file - R.R. legend?, 1923 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Elt. Miller / M., 1879 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - New York S., 1873-oct-18 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - N.Y. Tribune, 1977-mar-19 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Gould, 1878 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - CF Adams - pre 1880, 1879 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - CPH Ben Holladay, 1878 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - CP St. Sales, 1886 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Accounts w/ Gout, 1876 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - CP Finances - Europe, 1871-1879 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Bonds -- Speyeer Co., 1879 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - C.P. Internal Financial Transaction, 1876-1879 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Debt. Stodes -etc. C.P., 1875 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Bonds etc. Outside Private Court, 1875-1876 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - SP Bands, 1876 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - CP - Stock notes, 1873 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Bella Organized Complexity, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Brav.: Complete Thesis, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Creative Funding of Grand Trunk, 1853-1881 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Ann Carlos - Frank Las Can. Railroad - Role of Inf. (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Paul David - Why are Institutions the Carriers of History, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - 3 essays - Capital Market, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Grief: On the Social Foundations, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Grief: Econ. History Game Theory, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Grief: Micro Theory, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - NYC Banks Ntl. Banking System (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Williamson - Watersheds and Turning Points: C.W. Financing, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Gavin (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Harley, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Telegraph + Pac R.R., 1894 Jun (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Investment genl., 1999 (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Larry Neal - Move, Pit, Rsk (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Larry Neal - Integration of Capital Markets, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - Ripley R.R. France, 1915 (Box 20, Folder 70)
    - Cooley, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - Orsi - SP Reclamation, 1902-1930 (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - Taussig - State as Economic Factor, 1886 (Box 20, Folder 73)
    - Carey - Technology Ideology (Box 20, Folder 74)
    - Schwantes: Profs (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - Images R.R., 2002 (Box 20, Folder 76)
    - Robert Gordon Legal Thought, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 77)
    - Reactions to R.R. - C.P., 1867 (Box 20, Folder 78)
    - Conductors Story - Harpers, 1889 (Box 20, Folder 79)
    - Central Pacific, 1869 (Box 20, Folder 80)
    - Henry Wood Long Suffering Shareholders, 1889 (Box 20, Folder 81)
    - Harpers, 1886 (Box 20, Folder 82)
    - American Plutocracy as Care for Corrupt (Box 20, Folder 83)
    - Josiah Quiney, 1869 (Box 20, Folder 84)
    - William Z. Ripley Stickwatering, 1911 (Box 20, Folder 85)
    - Trust, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 86)
    - Williamson American Retardation, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 87)
    - Wallis, 1842-1852 (Box 20, Folder 88)
    - Weingasl + Walls, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 89)
    - Wilkins History of For. Inv., 1816 (Box 20, Folder 90)
    - CPH, 1884 Mar - Jun (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - CPH Incoming, 1884 Jul - Dec (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - CPH incoming, 1884 Jan - Jul (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - To CPH, 1885 Jan - Mar (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - To CPH, 1885 Apr - Jun (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - To CPH, 1885 Jul - Sep (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - To CPH, 1885 Oct - Dec (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Huntington to Gage - Hopkins Coll., 1886 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - CPH - incoming, 1886 Jan - Jul (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Incoming CPH, 1886 Jul - Dec (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - CPH - incoming, 1887 Jan - May (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Hopkins to Huntington, 1867 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Cipher, 1879 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Finishing sup., 1879 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Southern Pacific - cost. (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Oregon, 1878 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - SP. Genl. Arizona, 1879 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - C.P. S.P. legal series, 1875 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Sawyer - 5% case, 1877 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Salinas - Monterrey + C.P., 1878 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Ciphers, 1875 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Cohen: the California King, 1879 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Cohen (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Branan suit etc., 1873 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Tevis, 1879 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - A.A. Cohen - Huntington (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Cohen (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Cohen letter (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Railroad Cohen (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - RRs + Railroad corp, 1879 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Coal, 1870 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - S. P. Operations, 1873-1876 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Space (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Suits Against C.P. (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Stanford election, 1885-1886 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Southern Pacific - Reorg + strategy, 1875 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Labor, 1876 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - C. P. Huntington - Genl., 1899 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Colton Estate, 1876-1879 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Hopkins Estate, 1879 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Stanford finances, 1879 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Huntington finances, 1879 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Millionaires Houses, 1877 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - CPH Misc. personal (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Personal pleas, 1878 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Huntington's house, 1875 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Bierstadt, 1870s (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Dwinnel - Higher Reads of Continental railer, 1869 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Effects of publicity C.P., 1873-1876 (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Herald + Tribune Article, 1877 (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Stephen Masset - predictions on complete of Cub, 1869 May 1 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Lobbyists - misc, 1871-1877 (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Franchot corr., 1874 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Lobbying - flass - C.P., 1871-1878 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Tom Scott (quotes) (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Texas + Pacific 44th (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - Argument of tam scott (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - CP. Politics Colton, Huntington, 1876 (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - C.P. - Various Pds to check, 1878 (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - CP. Fisheries, 1874 (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - House Sporran + RR follow (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - Utah southern (Box 34, Folder 62)
    - CP AT + SF (see also Artell - NM) (Box 34, Folder 63)
    - CP/UP, 1875-1878 (Box 34, Folder 64)
    - Weather, accidents, etc., 1875 (Box 34, Folder 65)
    - Poor's manual - N.P., 1873-1874 (Box 34, Folder 66)
    - Poor's RR Manual - U.P., 1871-1872 (Box 34, Folder 67)
    - Poor's R.R. manual/-Letters, 1873 (Box 34, Folder 68)
    - Poors RR Manual - S.P., 1876-1877 (Box 34, Folder 69)
    - Poors RR manual - C.P., 1870-1871 (Box 34, Folder 70)
    - Chinese (Box 34, Folder 71)
    - Passenger travel - misc., 1874 (Box 34, Folder 72)
    - Salinas - S.P., 1874 (Box 34, Folder 73)
    - Petition - SP., 1876 (Box 34, Folder 74)
    - Powell Letters RR see also CPH, 1877 (Box 34, Folder 75)
    - Settlers, 1876 (Box 34, Folder 76)
    - Congress - Lobbying - public land, 1878 (Box 34, Folder 77)
    - Mussel slough, 1879 (Box 34, Folder 78)
    - Friends SP (Box 34, Folder 79)
    - Misc. articles Thurman Bill - Sinking Fud, 1870 (Box 34, Folder 80)
    - Chittonden - Wilson - Comm, 1873 (Box 34, Folder 81)
    - CPH, 1890 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Southern Pacific Company, 1890 May - Dec (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1882 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - CPH, 1892 Feb - Sep (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - CPH, 1892 Sep - Dec (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - CPH, 1892 Jan - Feb (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - CPH outgoing ser, 1892 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - CPH, 1893 Jan - Mar (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - CPH outgoing ser, 1892 Sep - Dec (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - CPH outgoing ser. 2, 1892 Jun - Sep (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - CPH, 1893 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - CPH, 1893 Apr - Jun (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - CPH, telegraphs, 1893 Jul - Aug (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - CPH, 1893 Sep - Nov (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - CPH - incoming ser 1, 1894 Jan - Mar (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - CPH ser 1, 1894 Jun (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - CPH incoming, 1894 Apr - May (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Contracts, 1860s (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Contract + finance co., 1873 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - (Toust) Associates personel, 1869 Jul (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Standards: Construction of Pac. R.R., 1866 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Standard Gov. Annual R. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - CPH, 1865-1866 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - CPH papers, 1861 Feb (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - CPH papers Crocker to Huntingter Construction, 1867 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Stanford - SLC letters, 1868-1869 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - CPH, 1871 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Assoc. to CPH, 1872 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Assoc. to CP + Tawne, 1873 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - The Octopus Speaks (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Stanford to CPH etc, 1875 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Assoc., 1875 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Assoc. cors, 1876 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Associate, 1877 Jul - Dec (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Associates, 1878 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Gates to CP, 1879 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Assoc. Corr., 1880 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - CPH, 1880 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - CPH, 1881 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - CPH, 1882-1883 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Huntington letterbooks, 1883 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - K, 1883 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Xerox, 1883 Jul - Dec (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Assoc. correspondence, 1879 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - CPH, 1884 Jan - Mar (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - The Roots of Dependency: Subsistence, Environment, and Social Change Among the Choctaws, Pawnees, and Navajos.
    - Land Grand Traverse Band, 1940-1970 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - G.T. New Material, 1898 -1903 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Leelanau Indians Comprehensive Plan, 1977 Dec (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - SSM, 1930s (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Mt. Pleasant School Records, 1920s (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Mt. Pleasant, 1896-1904 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Ottawas, 1930s (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Northern Michigan Ottawa Association, 1950-1951 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Michigan off. Correspondence, 1887-1895 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Lower Peninsula Bands, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Sault St. Marie -- Treaties (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - checks, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Ottawa Reorganization, 1930s (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Roman Law Burt Lake 20th Century, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Maps - Burt Lake (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Burt Lake, 1872 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Tax payments + redemptions, 1886-1914 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Burn out, 1900-1916 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Burt Lake new materials, 1911 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Burt Lake - Fed corr. (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Burt Lake Band Loss of Land (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Chapt. 3 G. T. (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Botanical Surveys, 1843-1897 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Prairie Plains Ecology: Village sites + faunal plant remains (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - As tribes of Mo. Relations w/Sioux, 1833-1864 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Tribes of upper Mo., 1820-1856 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Sioux see also Pawnee-mandan As., 1862 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Extra copy Sioux article (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Newspapers + summaries (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Burt Lake: Acquisition of Land, 1840 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Leelanau Indians Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Need replies (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - envelope (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Taxation genl. (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Grand Traverse -- sources (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - G. T., 1850s (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Smith Letter (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Annual reports -- CIA, 1880s (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Documents prior to 1855 treaty Grand traverse, 1803-1855 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Documents: Background to 1855 treaties (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Choctaw in Natchez War, 1773 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Choctaw Trade Technology (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Choctaw English Relations, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Present Fr. Vs. English Systems, 1748-1755 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Historical Account of the Revolt of the Chactan Indians (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Bancroft Library Materials - Choctaw, 1986-1995 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Choctaw - French Relations (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Red Shoes - Choctaw Civil War, 1745-1751 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Choctaw Politics, 1829-1831 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Choctaw-Chickasaw, 1750s (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Aitkin Choctaw - English Negotiation, 1750s (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Councils and Congress, 1763-1772 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Choctaw - Hunting, 1721-1791 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Middle Mississipi, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Choctaw - Environment First Hand accounts, 1722-1822 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Choctaw Bibliography, 1952-1953 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Rostlund - S.E. Bison, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Choctaw Population, 1721-1823 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Choctaw Politics, 1766-1775 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Choctaw Misc. Pol./ S., 1815-1827 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Choctaw Archeology, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Choctaw - to be refiled, 1806-1826 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Choctaw - Creek Relations, 1739-1787 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Bennett - Food Econ. Of N.E. Indians, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Choctaw - English, 1763-1776 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Choctaw Burning (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Census Material: Captains and Large Landholders (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Missions, 1823 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Choctaw - Fishing, 1775 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Choctaw - Animal behavior, ecology, 1819 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Choctaw Relations with tribes West of the Mississippi, 1765-1831 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Ecology -General (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Choctaw Problems: Notes (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Sectional Divisions in Nation: Trade, Eng-Fr., 1721-1784 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Choctaw Medicine and Disease, 1731-1829 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Ecology - Long-Leaf Pine (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Choctaw Villages and Towns, 1764-1975 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Econ. Anthro. -G., 1929 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Misc. Culture - Settlement Patterns, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Choctaw-Spanish Relations, 1767-1794 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Choctaw Settlements - West of Mississippi, 1805-1816 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Air Force Outline, 1798-1813 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Choctaw Trade (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Chap 5: Modernization (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Notes in use (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Choctaw Animals, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Black Belt, 1957-1971 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence with Vehik on Upper Republicans, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Pawnee Genl., 1805-1867 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Plains history: genl. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - 424, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Mo. River indians - genl., 1777-1799 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Horses, 1835-1844 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Upper republican, Nebraska Smoky Hill, Woodland (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Pawnee - pop. + see L. +C folder, 1820-1832 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Prairie ecology - sci. studies of prairie fires, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Pawnee - origins, bands village sites, 1775-1800 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Pawnee - As, 1843-1855 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Pawnee - Hunting + animals, 1804-1846 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Pawnee - Otoe, Mo, Omaha, Iowa inter-tribal relations, 1800-1853 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Dorsey + Murey (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Dunbar - Pawnee, 1880 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Plains ecology + environment, 1897 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Red Cloud - Indian Politics article, 1871 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Prairie + plains - mammals, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Prairie ecology - soils (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Prairie ecology - root systems, underground functions (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Prairie ecology - erosion, water interception, and runoff (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Prairies plant competition, 1924-1926 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Pine Ridge Escarpment, 1880-1890 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Grazing - effects on prairie vegetation - sci. studies (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Disease - govt., 1846 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Middle Missouri (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - The Newberry Library (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Ainu, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Shakers, 1882-1883 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Prehistoric Climates, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Pawnees - summer unsorted, 1874 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Prairie grasses - Species (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Prairie ecology - Shrub communities (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Woodlands in prairie regions (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Drought and prairie vegetation sci. studies, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Forest's ecology (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Prairie ecology (general) (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Pawnee - use of wild plants, 1835 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Pawnee Agency documents (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Pawnee - Genl. Condition + rants, 1870s (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - negatives for Pawnee article (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Pawnee - plains nomads, 1829-1844 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Pawnee Hist. sources, 1785 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Pawnee Chapter Emergency Copy, 1800 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Prairie and plains mussels, clams, fish, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Pawnee - New Materials, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Navajo Chap. 1, 1930 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Mex-sp - on Navajo, 1840 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Admin, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Stockwater - Erosion control, 1937 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Fonaroff - Diss. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - SCS - CCC Nav. Work programs, 1936 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Horse Reduction, 1937-1938 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Administration of Regs., 1941 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - CIA reports - Navajo, 1883-1885 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - U.M., 1936 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Tribal Council Resolutions (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Irrigation Projects fruitlands - etc., 1938 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Cal research (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Navajo - Grazing Cap. Mop, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Raleigh MA - Navajo (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Louise Lamphere - symbolic element ceremonial Co-op (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Range Management Reports see also land planning + integrated roots, 1936 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Fonaroff - Article (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Game genl., 1934 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Nav. Econ. Development (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - S. W. Ecology secondary, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Brugge - Nav. Diversification (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Roland Wagner … ritual syncretism… Reyotism (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Tuan: Gullies, 1917 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Cowgill - population increase, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Admin, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Navajo Project - Annual U.S.S.C.S. reports, 1935-1938 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Forestry reports Navajo Project, 1936 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - LMU 1, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - LMU 3, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Post- Morgan Opp. (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Nav.- Post 41, 1901-1941 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Administration, 1937 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Hill - As (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Nav. Biological bunch (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - PreCollier - policy, 1907 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Administration, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - revision (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Book intro. (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Steen - Grazing environ (Box 31, Folder 41)